var questions = [
    {
        question: "What is Buddy Rich's primary stick grip that he swore by?",
        choices: ["Match grip", "Traditional grip", "French grip", "Natural grip"],
        answer: "Traditional grip",
    },
    {
        question: "The official name of the drum stool you sit on is the ______________.",
        choices: ["Stump", "Highchair", "Rocker", "Throne"],
        answer: "Throne",
    },
    {
        question: "Paradiddles, anyone?",
        choices: ["RRLL LLRR", "RLRL LRLR", "RLRR LRLL", "RRRL LLLR"],
        answer: "RLRR LRLL",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is not a material drum shells are made of?",
        choices: ["Bronze", "Elephant bone", "Maple wood", "Acrylic"],
        answer: "Elephant bone",
    },
    {
        question: "John Bonham was the drummer for which band?",
        choices: ["Led Zeppelin", "The Beatles", "Van Halen", "Nickelback"],
        answer: "Led Zeppelin",
    },
    {
        question: "What is a drummer's #1 tool to tune drums?",
        choices: ["Drum fork", "Drum dial", "Drum key", "Drum stick"],
        answer: "Drum key",
    },
    {
        question: "What parts of the drum kit do you play in the pocket with?",
        choices: ["Stick, foot, and hands", "Crash, ride, and hi-hat", "Throne, pedal, and sticks", "Kick, snare, and hi-hat"],
        answer: "Kick, snare, and hi-hat",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the crazy drummer on the Muppet Show?",
        choices: ["Kermit", "Animal", "Gonzo", "Beaker"],
        answer: "Animal",
    },
    {
        question: "Part of this band's fame comes from their one-armed drummer, Rick Allen:",
        choices: ["Gun n Roses", "AC/DC", "Def Leppard", "Queen"],
        answer: "Def Leppard",
    },
    {
        question: "I've got a fever and the only prescription is _____________.",
        choices: ["Rock n Roll", "More cowbell", "Drums", "Acetaminophen"],
        answer: "More cowbell",
    },
];